<db>
    <personnage id="0">Elisabeth de Cerjeat was born in 1769 in Louth, Great Britain to a Swiss aristocrat father and a British mother. The family moves to La Rue de Bourg in Lausanne in 1780, where she, along with her sister, devotes her time to helping the poor. In 1843 at the age of 73, after being treated for cataracts, she founds an asylum for the blind, with the help of William Haldimand. She dies in Montchoisi in 1847.</personnage> 
    <personnage id="1">Angélique Trüschel, born in 1780, is the wife of Conrad Trüschel. The couple owns a brewery of the same name. The property consists of the main living quarters, a brewery, stables, a barn, a woodshed, a garden, and an orchard. It is there that she raises her daughters. Conrad dies in 1838 and Angélique in 1842.</personnage>
    <personnage id="2">Henri Perregaux, born in 1785 in Lausanne, is the quasi-designated architect of the state of Vaud. He works as a building inspector and a member of the committees responsible for both roadwork and bridges. He restores the cathedral of Lausanne, builds town halls, as well as the Grand-Pont bridge with the help of the engineer Adrien Pichard. He dies in Lausanne in 1850.</personnage>
    <personnage id="3">The baroness Isabelle de Montolieu is a writer born in 1751 in Lausanne. At age of 35, she anonymously publishes her first novel "Caroline de Lichtfield," which would become popular throughout Europe. She also translates many books into French, such as "Le Robinson Suisse" by Johann David Wyss and multiple works by Jane Austen. She dies in Vennes in 1932.</personnage>
    <personnage id="4">Jean-Jacques Mercier was born in 1789 in Lausanne. Both a tanner and a merchant, he establishes a leather industry by the Flon river, which has not yet been built over. The waste produced by the factory is thrown into the river, turning the valley into a smelly and unsanitary place. He dies in 1868 in Lausanne.</personnage>  
    <personnage id="5">Benedict Rochat was born in 1777 in Lausanne. Originally from the vallée de Joux, the Rochat family have been millers for generations and are spread across multiple mills by the Flon river. By using hydraulic power, they are able to grind cereals and saw wood, but due to the state of the water, they live in unhealthy living conditions.</personnage>
    <objectif id="-1">[b]Objective :[/b] 
Close the notebook and talk to M. Gély.</objectif>
    <objectif id="0">[b]Objective :[/b] 
Fill the first page of the notebook. The information can be found in the room.</objectif>
    <objectif id="1">[b]Objective :[/b]
Find the missing information to complete the registry and return to M. Gély once all the pages are done.
If you are unsure of an answer, you can ask M. Gély for help. He can correct the entries on your current page.</objectif>
</db>
